Guide to the Max S. Baucus Papers 1958-2016 (bulk 1974-2014)
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Senate: Press, 1978-2014; Series VIII; 41.1 linear feet; 15.3 gigabytes
  - Electronic Files, 1978-2014; Sub-series 5; 15.3 gigabytes
    - Speeches
      - "Korean Policy in 1998: The Roar of a Distant Waterfall," The Korea Society, June 2, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - QandA--Korea Society, June 2, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - National Summit on Retirement Savings (1), June 4, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - National Summit on Retirement Savings (2), June 4, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - National Summit on Retirement Savings (3), June 4, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Girls State, June 7, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Preparations for Clinton Trip to China, June 11, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Meet the Press interview, June 14, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Tough Questions, Meet the Press, June 14, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Hong Kong One Year Later," The Asia Society, June 15, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "The Budget and Environmental Protection", June 15, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Morning Newsmaker, National Press Club (1), July 8, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Morning Newsmaker, National Press Club (2), July 8, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Morning Newsmaker, National Press Club (3), July 8, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - U.S.-China Business Council (1), July 15, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - U.S.-China Business Council (2), July 15, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - U.S.-China Business Council (3), July 15, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - U.S.-China Business Council (4), July 15, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - U.S.-China Business Council (5), July 15, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Pension Bill Press Conference (1), July 21, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Pension Bill Press Conference (2), July 21, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Congressional Economic Leadership Institute, July 22, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Engaging China in the 21st Century", July 24, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Press conference to announce Bipartisan Patient Bill of Rights, July 29, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - DSCC (Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee) Trip to China and U.S-China International Relations, July 30, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Major Issues in Building Up U.S.-China Relationship for the 21st Century," Lincoln Lectureship, July 30, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Major Issues in Building Up U.S.-China Relationship for the 21st Century", July 30, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - TEA-21 Surrogate Stump Speech, August 14, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Statement, Release of the President's Grand Jury Deposition, September 11, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points, Release of the President's Grand Jury Deposition, September 20, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Three Threats to the American Presidency", October 1, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Dennis Nettles' Radio Show KBOW Butte, October 8, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Trade and Congress: The Coming Term," Information Technology Industry Council, October 22, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Mansfield-Metcalf Dinner, November 1, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - U.S.-ASEAN (Association of Southeast Asian Nations) Business Council, December 2, 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Canyon Ferry Statement, circa 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points, Canyon Ferry Bill, circa 1998 (Digital file Digital File)
      - QandA Pre-State of the Union Thoughts, January 19, 1999 (Digital file Digital File)
      - American Methanol Institute, February 5, 1999 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Remarks to the 56th Montana Legislative Assembly, February 18, 1999 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Mansfield-Metcalf Dinner, March 27, 1999 (Digital file Digital File)
      - On the Occasion of the Visit of Chinese Ambassador Li Zhaoxing, April 23, 1999 (Digital file Digital File)
      - On the Occasion of the Visit of Chinese Ambassador Li Zhaoxing, Agricultural Leaders Roundtable, April 24, 1999 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana State University Commencement (1), May 15, 1999 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana State University Commencement (2), May 15, 1999 (Digital file Digital File)
      - CNN Late Edition Transcript, May 16, 1999 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana AFL-CIO, May 21, 1999 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Yellowstone County Truman Dinner, May 22, 1999 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana Behavioral Initiative, June 21, 1999 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Institute for International Economics Conference on China and WTO (World Trade Organization) Accession, June 29, 1999 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Royal Teton Ranch, August 31, 1999 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points on Transportation Appropriations Bill, September 1, 1999 (Digital file Digital File)
      - California Street Bridge Dedication, October 9, 1999 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Remarks for HELP, October 18, 1999 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Gun Show Talking Points, circa 1999 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Flathead Vets meeting, January 28, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "How Can the WTO (World Trade Organization) Survive Seattle?", January 31, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "How Can the WTO (World Trade Organization) Survive Seattle?" Economic Strategy Institute Forum, February 3, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - The Cattlemen's Convention, Ranchers-Cattlemen Action Legal Fund (1), February 4, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - The Cattlemen's Convention, Ranchers-Cattlemen Action Legal Fund (2), February 4, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "China, the WTO (World Trade Organization), and the Future of U.S.-China Relations," Brookings Institution, March 27, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Ambassador Yuri Ushakov and U.S.-Russia Trade Relations, April 3, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - AIPAC (American Israel Public Affairs Committee), April 9, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Middle East Peace Process, April 9, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - University of Montana Commencement, May 13, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - National Lewis and Clark Educational Center Press Conference, May 25, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Economic Development Summit Talking Points, May 28, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana Stockgrowers Convention Mid-Year Meeting, June 9, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Missouri River protection, June 13, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Opening Remarks, Montana Economic Development Summit, June 25, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "e-America: How to Leverage Winning e-Business Strategies" (1), July 30, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "e-America: How to Leverage Winning e-Business Strategies" (2), July 30, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Rule of Law: Asia Perspectives," Mansfield Center for Pacific Affairs, October 22, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Flathead Veterans Meeting, November 28, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Pharmacy Dedication--Columbia Falls Vet Home, November 28, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Veterans", November 28, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Missoula Vets Meeting, November 29, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana Stockgrowers and Montana Grain Growers Associations, November 30, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Democratic Central Committee Elections, December 1, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Talking Points on National Security," U.S.-China, Taiwan Relations, December 7, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - American Chamber of Commerce in Beijing, December 10, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Economic Development Summit, December 10, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Tough Questions, AmCham, December 12, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - American Chamber of Commerce-Beijing, December 13, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points for Press Conference in China, December 13, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - American Chamber of Commerce-Korea, December 15, 2000 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points for Governor Judy Martz, Economic Development Meeting, February 19, 2001 (Digital file Digital File)
      - U.S. Chamber of Commerce Board of Directors, February 26, 2001 (Digital file Digital File)
      - AdvaMed, March 6, 2001 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Health in Rural Areas Act Talking Points, May 1, 2001 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Women's Economic Summit, May 22, 2001 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Agricultural Trade in the Next Decade," Commodity Club, June 12, 2001 (Digital file Digital File)
      - American Petroleum Institute (1), June 14, 2001 (Digital file Digital File)
      - American Petroleum Institute (2), June 14, 2001 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Shelby Chamber of Commerce Luncheon, July 5, 2001 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Havre Chamber of Commerce Luncheon, July 6, 2001 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Baucus-Rehburg Highway Roundtable Meeting, August 16, 2001 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Highway Policy Committee, Associated General Contractors, October 10, 2001 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Role in Next Highway Bill," Associated General Contractors, October 10, 2001 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "American Sheep Industry", February 6, 2002 (Digital file Digital File)
      - VFW (Veterans of Foreign Wars), May 30, 2002 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Homeland Security Town Hall Meeting, May 31, 2002 (Digital file Digital File)
      - NCFC (National Council of Farmer Cooperatives), June 10, 2002 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana Newspaper Association, July 1, 2002 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Community Transportation Association of America, January 1, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Iraq" (1), January 1, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Iraq" (2), January 1, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "The U.S. and Europe: Trading Partners or Trading Adversaries?" The New Atlantic Initiative, February 13, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points, 1996 Telecommunications Act, March 4, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Middle School Telephone Interview, March 14, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points, Agriculture and Iraq, March 19, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Remarks to the 58th Montana Legislative Assembly, March 21, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points, Wolves, March 1, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Cuba: Isolation or Engagement?" Carter Center, April 4, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Portland Business Alliance, April 10, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana Credit Union, May 1, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Helena Education Foundation's Celebration of Excellence (1), May 6, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Helena Education Foundation's Celebration of Excellence (2), May 6, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points, Medicare Press Conference, June 5, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points, Finance Democrats Meeting, June 9, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points, Caucus Lunch, June 10, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - American Petroleum Institute, June 14, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - ISI-SG Cowen Health Policy Conference, July 9, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points, Amtrak, July 30, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana Trial Attorneys, July 31, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Dennison call talking points, July 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "2-Year Anniversary of September 11", September 11, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - MTA Speech, September 22, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "S. 1039, The Wastewater Treatment Security Act of 2003 Minority Views", September 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points, Story Mansion SAE (Sigma Alpha Epsilon) House, October 2, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points, Rural Health Care Provisions, October 28, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Country of Origin Labeling Will Help Boost Montana's Ag Economy", October 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Veterans Day, November 11, 2003 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "The Economic Context for the JOBS Bill", March 1, 2004 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Cuba: Isolation or Engagement?" Carter Center, April 4, 2004 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Dinosaur Field Station, April 16, 2004 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "International Trade Creates Montana Jobs", July 9, 2004 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Working Together to Boost Montana's Natural Resource Economy", July 2004 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Carter Partnership Greeting, November 1, 2004 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana Aviation Conference, November 1, 2004 (Digital file Digital File)
      - ABA (American Bar Association) Washington Healthcare Summit, December 6, 2004 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana Air National Guard Wins Three National Awards, February 1, 2005 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana Broadcasters Association Convention, September 14, 2005 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana Hospital Association, September 14, 2005 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Women in Agriculture", October 11, 2005 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Meth Project Roundtable Opening Statement, January 23, 2006 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Montana Credit Unions", April 21, 2006 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points, DPC Meth Town Hall, September 27, 2006 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Meth Message, January 11, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Protecting Montanan Jobs on the Highway Bill", January 30, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Booking EDU Remarks, January 1, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points, New Tech, January 1, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - American Trucking Association (1), February 13, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - American Trucking Association (2), February 13, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Benefis Tragedy", February 14, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana Rural Water Systems Annual Conference, February 22, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Education", March 20, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - AIPAC (American Israel Public Affairs Committee) Lunch, March 30, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana Wildlife Federation Annual Meeting, April 21, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Board of Regents Meeting, May 31, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - U.S. Chamber of Commerce, June 5, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana Democratic Convention, August 4, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Community Jobs Forum, August 7, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Economic Development in Rural America, Montana Telecommunications Association (1), August 8, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Economic Development in Rural America, Montana Telecommunications Association (2), August 8, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Rural Philanthropy" (1), August 9, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Rural Philanthropy" (2), August 9, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Town Hall Meeting on CHIP (Children's Health Insurance Program), August 14, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points, Highway Trust Fund, September 7, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - National Association of Children's Hospitals, September 19, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Flathead County Democratic Dinner, September 29, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "A New Democratic Trade Policy," NDN, October 2, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Faith Community Impact Summit (1), October 9, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Faith Community Impact Summit (2), October 9, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Alternative Energy: Global Public Policy and Regulatory Challenges," Goldman Sachs Symposium, October 16, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Ideas Montana Medicine Conference, November 2, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Montana Cattlemen", November 3, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana Farm Bureau Annual Meeting, November 8, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - MCT (Missoula Children's Theater) and Bresnan Corporate Partnership Summit, November 10, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - AIPAC (American Israel Public Affairs Committee) Board, November 13, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Rocky Mountain Ballet Theatre, November 16, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Progressive Policy Institute, November 27, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - A Breakfast Honoring American Indian and Alaskan Native Children and Families Involved with the Foster Care System, December 11, 2007 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Speech to Contractors, January 9, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Washington Business Forum, January 23, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - University of Montana Focus the Nation, January 28, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Trade Adjustment Assistance," Peterson Institute for International Economics, January 30, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Crow and the State of Montana Signing Ceremony, February 6, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - AARP (American Association of Retired Persons) Board of Directors, February 14, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Social Security", February 14, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Campaign Announcement, Billings-Bozeman Rallies, February 19, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Funeral of Crow Tribal Chairman Carl Venne, February 19, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - White House Fiscal Summit, February 23, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - National Congress of American Indians, March 3, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Credit Union National Association, March 5, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - SFC Roundtable on Value-Based Purchasing, March 6, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Providence Health and Services Conference, March 8, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana Agriculture Bankers, March 27, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Mansfield-Metcalf Dinner, April 5, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana Health Care Forum, April 13, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Dinner in Honor of Korean President Lee, American Chamber of Commerce, April 17, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - University of Montana Native American Center, April 24, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - The Council on Competitiveness, April 30, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Agriculture and Farm Bill, May 3, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Beer Wholesalers, May 13, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points, Healthcare Summit meeting, May 14, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points, Land Park Announcement, May 23, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Memorial Day Groundbreaking, June 1, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Missoula Spring Fundraising Dinner, June 1, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talkers discussion with Senator Crapo, Health Care Summit, June 1, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - New Frontiers Conference, June 2, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - St. Mary Bridge Replacement Groundbreaking Event, July 18, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Traderoots Event, August 13, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Currents of Change and Opportunity: Navigating the Asian Pacific", September 5, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Picturing a Services Export Agenda," Coalition of Service Industries, September 17, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Election Night, November 4, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - A.W.A.R.E. Awards Banquet, November 25, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Diplomatic Academy of Vietnam, December 17, 2008 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Commonwealth Fund Congressional Health Policy Conference, January 11, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - TARP (Troubled Asset Relief Program) Assistance to Small Business, January 13, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Harvesting Clean Energy Conference, January 25, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Academy Health Conference, February 3, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - 61st Montana Legislative Assembly, February 18, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana Rural Water Conference, February 19, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - "Health Reform," White House Fiscal Summit, February 23, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Nonprofit Capacity Building Initiative, March 24, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Health Care Roundtable, April 21, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Health Care Roundtable, May 5, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Talking Points, Taxes, May 6, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - The Hill-AstraZeneca Breakfast Policy Briefing, May 7, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Health Roundtable, May 11, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Financing Health Care Roundtable, May 12, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Winifred High School Graduation, May 16, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Press QandAs for Panama Hearing, May 21, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - ISI Group Policy Health Conference (1), May 28, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - ISI Group Policy Health Conference (2), May 28, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Helena High School Commencement, June 6, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - American Group Medical Association, June 17, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Tough Questions from Liberals on Health Care Reform, June 29, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Groundbreaking Ceremony for Western Transportation Institute, August 19, 2009 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Helena Rotary Club, February 17, 2010 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana Rural Water Systems 31st Annual Conference, February 18, 2010 (Digital file Digital File)
      - North Fork Reception (1), April 28, 2010 (Digital file Digital File)
      - North Fork Reception (2), April 28, 2010 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Nomination Hearing of Alan Bersin, Commissioner of Customs, May 13, 2010 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Montana Democratic Platform Convention, June 11, 2010 (Digital file Digital File)
      - American Highway User Alliance, June 23, 2010 (Digital file Digital File)
      - APEC (Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation) Host Committee Launch, July 14, 2010 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Washington International Trade Association Annual Awards Dinner, July 21, 2010 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Billings Downtown Exchange Club Monthly Lunch (1), August 10, 2010 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Billings Downtown Exchange Club Monthly Lunch (2), August 10, 2010 (Digital file Digital File)
      - Community Transportation Association of America, August 23, 2010 (Digital file Digital File)